barneyswarehouse.com 2018-10-29

# Barneys Warehouse Site

## Introduction

Thank you for visiting Barneys New York online. The below policies apply to Barneys.com, BarneysWarehouse.com, TheWindow.Barneys.com, Barneys New York for iPhone App, Barneys New York for iPad App, and The Window from Barneys New York App. Your trust and information is extremely important to us at Barneys New York.

## Secure Ordering

Protecting your online order information on Barneys.com is very important to us. In our shopping checkout process, we use Secure Socket Layering (SSL), the industry-standard encryption technology that ensures the safety and security of your online order. When the letters "http" in the URL address change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL. 

Making a credit card purchase is just as safe on our web site as it is by telephone. But if you prefer to order merchandise from the website by phone, call toll-free 1-888-222-7639. Our customer service associates are available, Monday - Friday, 9 AM - 9 PM, and Saturday - Sunday, 10:30 AM - 7 PM, ET. 

## Privacy Policy

At Barneys New York, we are committed to providing you the finest products along with excellent service. In order to accomplish this, we gather, use and share certain personal information. Our online privacy policy describes what we gather, with whom we share it, and how you may direct us not to share certain information with certain parties. Because the security of your personal information is very important to us, we restrict access to your nonpublic personal information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your nonpublic personal information. 

## Information Collection

Whenever you shop with Barneys New York (in our stores, online, on our mobile applications or by phone) we obtain from you the information we need to complete your transaction. This may include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card or gift card number. We also retain details of your specific product purchases and transactions with us. If you register with us online, we may ask for additional information, such as your birthday, gender, or product preferences. If you interact with our mobile site or mobile applications, we may retain further details including device information, as well as push notification and location services you request. 

To improve your shopping experience, we may collect non-personal information about how users navigate throughthe site. We, and potentially our carefully selected third parties, may use cookies to collect information about how you browse and interact with our web site. A cookie is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device (hard drive). We may collect information such as your browser type, operating system, and general location information. Collecting this information through the use of cookies also helps us to prevent fraud. 

## Use And Disclosure Of Information

We use the information we collect to process your purchase transactions, to send you marketing and promotional materials by mail or e-mail, and to help us improve our store and online product assortments and services for you. 

We may provide information we collect to third party service providers that help us bring you our products and services, for example, a company that distributes our catalogs. 

We may provide information we collect to carefully selected third parties when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you. 

## Opt Out Procedures

If you prefer that we not disclose non-public personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures, that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures. If you wish to opt out of disclosures to nonaffiliated parties, you may do so by writing to Barneys New York, Attn. Marketing, 575 Fifth Avenue, New York NY 10017 or e-mailing webservices@barneys.com. 

## Changes To This Policy

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. We will communicate any such changes by updating this page, notifying you by email if you have registered your email address with us, or in writing, as required by law. 

## Barneys New York Credit Card Privacy Policy

If you have a Barneys New York credit card, a separate privacy policy describes collection, use, and protection of information about you and your account. To obtain a copy of our credit card privacy policy call 1-800-926-5393, or write Barneys New York, PO Box 326, Lyndhurst NJ 07071-0326. 

## Children's Privacy

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act imposes certain requirements on web sites directed at children under 13 that collect information on those children, and on web sites that knowingly collect information on children under 13. Barneys.com is not directed at children under 13, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13. 

## Online Account Registration

Registering with Barneys.com will make your online shopping faster and easier. We can store your shipping addresses and billing information so that you don’t have to enter them each time you shop. You will also be able to save your shopping basket, check your order status, and review your order history. In addition, you can seamlessly shop your favorite designers and products by saving them to your account. Your registered information will be securely stored with us, and you can add, delete, or change your registered information at any time by logging into your account. 

## Mobile

Barneys New York offers mobile applications (“apps”) that allow you to shop online, discover in-store happenings, browse editorial content, or receive other communications. All personal information collected by Barneys New York from your mobile device is protected by this Privacy Policy. 

Although you do not have to provide your location to use our mobile applications, allowing Barneys New York to collect precise location data enables us to deliver relevant content within our stores and to enhance your overall shopping experience. If you allow us to collect location information, we may collect your location at your request (such as when you tap “Enable” on a location services prompt). We may also collect location information when your device is near our in-store content personalization systems, even if you are not actively using the app. We use your location data to enhance your shopping experience, as well as to assist with foot traffic measurement and service improvements in our stores. You may turn off this location tracking at any time in your device settings, or by disabling Bluetooth. 

## E-Mails

We may send promotional e-mails to you only if you have asked to receive them. Each time you receive an e-mail from us, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" or stop receiving them.
